{
    "name": "examen octobre verbes",
    "id": "__iD__",
    "enabled": false,
    "author": "Martin Merkli",
    "copyright": "Public domain",
    "content": [
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                0
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "lieben/gerne haben",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " aimer",
            "solutions": [
                " aimer"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                1
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "beginnen/anfangen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " commencer",
            "solutions": [
                " commencer"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                2
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "essen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " manger",
            "solutions": [
                " manger"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                3
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "heben",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " lever",
            "solutions": [
                " lever"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                4
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "aufstehen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " se lever",
            "solutions": [
                " se lever"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                5
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "reinigen/putzen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " nettoyer",
            "solutions": [
                " nettoyer"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                6
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "abtrocknen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " essuyer",
            "solutions": [
                " essuyer"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                7
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "gehen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " aller",
            "solutions": [
                " aller"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                8
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "\u00f6ffnen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " ouvrir",
            "solutions": [
                " ouvrir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                9
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "rennen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " courir",
            "solutions": [
                " courir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                10
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "anbieten",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " offrir",
            "solutions": [
                " offrir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                11
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "l\u00fcgen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " mentir",
            "solutions": [
                " mentir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                12
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "pfl\u00fccken",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " cueillir",
            "solutions": [
                " cueillir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                13
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "beenden",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " finir",
            "solutions": [
                " finir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                14
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "sterben",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " mourir",
            "solutions": [
                " mourir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                15
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "kommen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " venir",
            "solutions": [
                " venir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                16
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "halten",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " tenir",
            "solutions": [
                " tenir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                17
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "schlafen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " dormir",
            "solutions": [
                " dormir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                18
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "weggehen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " partir",
            "solutions": [
                " partir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                19
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "ausgehen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " sortir",
            "solutions": [
                " sortir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                20
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "f\u00fchlen/sp\u00fcren",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " sentir",
            "solutions": [
                " sentir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                21
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "bedienen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " servir",
            "solutions": [
                " servir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                22
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "sich bedienen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " se servir",
            "solutions": [
                " se servir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        },
        {
            "id": [
                "__iD__",
                23
            ],
            "includes-image": false,
            "includes-answer-image": false,
            "question": "fliehen",
            "links": [],
            "solution": " fuir",
            "solutions": [
                " fuir"
            ],
            "tolerance": 2,
            "difficulty": 1,
            "frequency": 1.0
        }
    ]
}